Hi, welcome to session six,
嗨，欢迎来到第六节课，
in this session, we're going to talk about minor seventh chords and suspended chords,
在这节课中，我们将讨论小七和弦和挂留和弦，
if we have a little bit more color in them
如果我们有更多的色彩，
than the basic chords that we've been talking about so far,
比起我们讨论过的基本和弦，
but they still are open chords, that involve open strings.
但它们仍然是开放和弦，包括空弦。
We're also going to talk about strumming
我们还会讨论扫弦，
and strumming with ties which gets a little bit more complicated,
扫弦加延音线，这会变得有点复杂，
but sure makes it sound a little bit more musically interesting,
但肯定会让它听起来更有趣，
when we do it,
当我们弹奏的时候，
in the guitar tips section,
在吉他技巧部分，
we're going to talk about practicing strumming patterns without music,
我们会讨论在没有音乐的情况下练习扫弦模式，
we'll work with music here,
我们在这里会在有音乐的情况下练习，
but I also want to talk about doing it without music,
但我也想谈谈没有音乐的情况，
because that's the kind of situations, that you're going to be in,
因为你会遇到这样的情况，
when you're trying to play with friends or in a group situation like that.
当你试图和朋友一起演奏或在这样的集体场合中时。
So let's go ahead and get started.
所以让我们继续并开始吧。
Okay, now let's talk about the minor seventh chords,
好的，现在我们来讨论一下小七和弦，
three minor seventh chords, we're gonna cover in this, this section,
我们将在这一节讲到三个小七和弦，
Am7, Dm7 and Em7,
Am7 Dm7 Em7 ，
abbreviated A little m 7,
是 A m 7 的缩写，
the little m and the 7 is telling you it's a minor seventh chord,
m 和 7 告诉你它是小七和弦，
so let's look at that Am7 chord first,
所以让我们先来看看那个 Am7 和弦，
okay five string chord,
好的，五根弦的和弦，
everything in the family is going to be a five string chord,
家族中的所有东西都是五根弦的和弦，
so there's nothing happening on that six string.
所以在第六弦上不会发生任何事情。
We have open A,
我们有空弦 A ，
second finger on E,
中指在 E 上面，
open G,
空弦 G ，
first fingers C
食指在 C 上面，
and open E,
空弦 E ，
just play it altogether.
一起弹奏一下。
It's kind of like a C chord,
这像是 C 和弦，
if you take your third finger off,
如果你把无名指拿开，
pretty much the same thing.
很像是一样的东西。
Now let's talk about Dm7,
现在让我们来谈谈 Dm7 ，
this one is a little bit different from the others,
这个和其他的有点不同，
it's a four string chord,
这是一个四根弦的和弦，
all the D's are four string chord,
所有的 D 都是四根弦的和弦，
so let's look what's happening here,
所以让我们看看这里发生了什么，
we've got open D,
我们有空弦 D ，
I've got my second finger on this A
我的中指在这个 A 上，
and here's the problem right here,
这就是问题所在，
I need to put my first finger,
我需要把食指放在这里，
he needs to cover two strings at once,
他需要同时覆盖两根弦，
needs to pull double duty,
需要拉双重任务，
I've got an F and I've also got a C,
我有一个 F ，我还有一个 C ，
that I need to cover,
我需要覆盖，
now I guess I could really do that,
我想我可以这样做，
that's not the right way to do it,
这不是正确的方式，
put your second finger on that A
把你的中指放在 A 上，
and then I want you to put your first finger down over both of those strings,
然后我想你把你的食指放在这两根弦上，
now, this that's the we're in the baby pool of barre chords,
这是我们在横按和弦的婴儿游泳池中，
this is the introduction to barre chords,
这是横按和弦的介绍，
let me show you,
让我演示给你看，
so let me talk about this for saying,
所以让我来谈谈这个，
it's a pretty big concept.
这是一个相当大的概念。
What you don't want to do is raise this wrist up,
你不想做的是抬起这个手腕，
because it's hard to push down those two strings,
因为那两根弦很难往下推，
you raise that wrist up,
你把手腕抬起来，
you crank this up here
你在这里抬起来，
and you end up doing something like this,
你最后会做这样的事情，
now it may work a little bit,
现在它可能会起一点作用，
but when we get to more complex barre chords,
但当我们达到更复杂的横按和弦时，
you'll see that that is not going to work very very well at all,
你会发现这不能很好的工作，
so here's what you need to do,
所以这是你需要做的，
lower that wrist,
降低手腕，
put your finger out,
把手指伸出去，
your joint will go in,
你的关节就会伸进去，
but it will also go a little bit inverted, not very much,
但它也会有一点倒过来，不是很多，
but I'll go a little bit inverted,
但我会倒过来一点，
it's the inverted,
这是倒过来的，
how the muscles are there is,
肌肉是怎样的，
how you do these barre chords,
你如何做这些横按和弦，
especially these little ones like that,
特别是像这样的小和弦，
get your two, get your finger over those two strings, kind of invert that,
让你的手指放在这两根弦上，类似于倒转，
that's a good way to get a lot of pressure focused into one spot,
这是一个让很多压力集中在一个点上的好方法，
if you try and do it
如果你试着做，
by just putting your, raising your wrist and pulling your finger back
抬起你的手腕，向后拉你的手指，
is not a very efficient way to do it,
不是一个非常有效的方法来做这件事，
put that wrist down, put that finger in front, pressing down,
把手腕放下，把手指放在前面，按下，
inverting that first finger, catching that,
翻转食指，抓住它，
now trying to add that A to it,
现在把 A 加进去，
so now look what I've got going,
所以现在看看我得到了什么，
I've got one joint that's going normal,
我得到了一个关节正常，
one that's going inverted,
一个关节翻转，
I'm doing two different things with two different joint, joints,
我用两个不同的关节做两个不同的事情，
it's a little bit tricky to do it first,
首先做这个有点棘手，
but that's the Dm7,
但这就是 Dm7 ，
once you do it a couple times,
一旦你做了几次，
you'll get, you'll get the hang of.
你就会掌握诀窍。
Okay, the last one is an Em7,
好的，最后一个是 Em7 ，
we're going to talk about E's family chords six strings,
我们将讨论 E 家族和弦是六根弦，
okay, it's two different fingerings we can use,
好的，我们可以使用两个不同的指法，
two different alternate fingerings on this,
使用两个不同的指法，
let me teach you the first one,
让我来教你们第一个，
this one I like,
这个是我喜欢的那个，
don't necessarily have to do it like I do,
不一定要像我一样做，
there's different guys do it different ways.
有不同的人做它的方式不同。
Open E,
空弦 E ，
now I put my first finger on this B,
现在把我的食指放在 B 上面，
then I have two open strings and D and G,
然后我有两根空弦， D 和 G ，
then I have my third finger on this high D,
然后我的无名指在高音 D 上，
my pinky on this high G,
我的小拇指高音 G 上，
Em7.
Em7 。
Now another way to do that,
现在，另一种方法来做这个，
which I think is a little bit more awkward,
我认为这有点困难，
so it's been a bit more awkward to me,
对我来说有点困难，
but a lot of guys use it,
但很多人使用它，
is an open E,
是一个空弦 E ，
second finger up here on this B,
中指在 B 上面，
third finger on this E,
无名指在 E 上面，
G,
G ，
pinky covering D,
小拇指按住 D ，
the last string open,
最后一根弦空弦，
now you'll notice the finger is completely different for this one,
你会注意到手指是完全不同的，
how can it be the same chord,
怎么可能是同一个和弦，
well chord is just a combination of tones,
和弦只是音调的组合，
no matter how many ways I slice them,
不管我用多少方法切分它们，
there's still chords,
仍然有和弦，
there's still the same chord,
仍然有相同的弦，
so it doesn't matter really what order I have the notes in,
所以我把音符放在什么顺序并不重要，
so here's version one,
所以这是版本一，
here's version two,
这是版本二，
either way you can use fun
无论你用哪种方式，
and whatever lanes better with your hand,
无论哪个适合你的手，
let's do some of the minor chord exercises.
让我们做一些小和弦练习。
Okay, basic open chord exercises using minor sevenths,
好的，使用小七的基本开放和弦练习，
look at number one there, we have Am,
看看第一个，我们有 Am ，
and then we're gonna go to Am7,
然后我们要跳到 Am7 ，
the rhythms you'll notice you're getting a little more complex as well,
你会注意到节奏也变得更复杂了，
let's do it real slowly.
让我们慢慢地做。
Ready, go,
准备，开始，
Am7, now take that third finger off,
Am7 ，现在把无名指拿开，
D7, now,
现在 D7 ，
three Gs in a row,
连续的三个 G ，
How did you do, let's try one more time.
你做得怎么样，我们再试一次。
Ready, play,
准备，弹奏，
third finger off,
无名指拿开，
D7
D7 ，
three G in a row.
连续的三个 G 。
Okay, now let's do exercise number two,
好的，现在让我们做第二个练习，
this one starts on a D
这个从 D 开始，
and this gives us a good workout on that Em7 chord.
给我们一个很好 Em7 和弦的练习。
Okay, starts on a D, nice and slow,
好的，从 D 开始，慢慢地，
ready, play,
准备，弹奏，
Em7, take a second to get to it,
Em7 ，花点时间找到它，
either form you want to use is fine,
你想用的哪个形式都可以，
Am7, D,
Am7 D ，
G.
G 。
Very good, let's try one more time,
很好，让我们再试一次，
D, Em7, D 1 2, G.
D Em7 ， D 1 2 ， G 。
Great okay, now let's scoot down the page a little bit to number three,
好的，现在让我们把这一页滑下来一点到练习三，
I was going to go down farther,
我本想再往下走，
but let's do number three,
但我们来做练习三，
that gives us a good workout on the Dm7,
这让我们在 Dm7 上有一个很好的练习，
okay, pretty simple rhythm,
好的，非常简单的节奏，
it's the same rhythm for all the four measures,
所有四个小节的节奏都是一样的，
let's start on that C,
让我们从那个 C 开始，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
one two, same thing,
1 2 ，相同的东西，
now here's that Dm7,
现在这里是 Dm7 ，
make sure you form it correctly,
确保你使用正确的形式，
inverting that first finger,
食指向内翻，
here we go,
我们开始，
four string chord,
四根弦的和弦，
back to C repeat,
回到 C ，重复，
Dm7, go,
Dm7 ，开始，
very good.
很好。
Okay before we talk about suspended chords,
好的，在我们讨论挂留和弦之前，
when you talk about strumming for a second,
我们先来讨论一下扫弦，
because we're getting more complex with our rhythms,
因为我们的节奏变得越来越复杂了，
there strumming is going to have to change a little bit as well,
扫弦也需要稍微改变一下，
let's talk about good technique for strumming,
我们来谈谈关于扫弦的好的技巧，
now at this point, we've pretty much just been going down down down down,
在这一点上，我们几乎一直在下下下下，
we need to do an up,
我们需要做一个上，
there'll be a bunch of [] row
会有很多[]列，
and we'll go down up, down up, down up, down up,
我们会做下上下上下上下上，
even when you are doing just downs,
即使你在做下的时候，
your hand is still doing a silent up,
你的手仍然做了一个无声的上，
if you think about it,
如果你这样想的话，
okay, so your hand is always doing this cycle,
好的，所以你的手总是在做这个循环，
down up, down up, down up, down,
下上，下上，下上，下，
it's kind of a piston in a car,
就像汽车里的活塞，
it's always going down up, down up, down up, down up,
它总是下上，下上，下上，下上，
okay, so when I'm practicing this strumming,
好的，当我练习扫弦的时候，
now we're going to get a little more complex,
现在我们会变得更复杂，
be thinking of that,
要考虑到这一点，
so you don't want to go down down down down down,
所以你不想做下下下下下，
that would be wrong,
这是错误的，
down, down up, down, down,
下，下上，下，下，
if you want good smooth strumming,
如果你想要很好的流畅地弹奏，
see how if I do all downs, it sounds a little bit different
看看如果我做所有下，它听起来有点不同，
and as we get more complex,
当我们变得更复杂时，
it's going to really start throwing you off,
它会开始让你[离开]，
it's going to make sure you understand what we're doing,
这将确保你理解我们在做什么，
I'm never going to tell you to be up,
我永远不会告诉你上，
when you're in the cycle to be down or the opposite,
当你处于循环中的下降或相反时，
it may be a little confusing at first,
一开始可能有点困惑，
but pretty soon you'll realize that,
但很快你就会意识到，
that's really the only way you could do it,
这是你真正能做到的唯一方法，
if you keep that cycle consistent,
如果你保持这个循环的一致性，
okay, that's about strumming.
好的，这是关于扫弦。
Now, let's talk about adding ties into the, inside of our strumming chords,
现在让我们来讨论一下在扫弦中添加延音线，
okay, so just on a G chord,
所以在 G 和弦上，
let's do exercise number one.
让我们做第一个练习。
Okay, the first part of exercise number one is without the tie
好的，练习一的第一部分是不加延音线，
and the second part I through in the tie,
第二部分加了延音线，
your strumming pattern is going to change just slightly,
你的扫弦模式会有轻微的变化，
but the up and down cycle of your hand is the same,
但你的手的上下循环是一样的，
whether I'm hitting the strings or not hitting the strings.
无论我是拨动弦还是不拨动弦。
Number one, A, on a G chord,
第一个， A ，在 G 和弦上，
down, down up, down,
下，下上，下，
okay, one more time, down up, down,
好的，再来一次，下上，下，
now even though it's just a half note,
即使只是二分音符，
I want you to keep your hand going,
我希望你的手保持移动，
very important concept,
非常重要的概念，
keep your hand going
保持你的手移动，
or you're going to forever get turned around on where you need to be playing,
否则你将永远[转向]在哪里弹奏，
the secret is,
这里的秘密是，
let me tell you the secret,
让我告诉你秘密，
for somebody's done it for years,
一些人已经做了很多年，
keep your hand going, okay, down, down up, down,
保持你的手移动，下，下上，下，
now I know you're saying yourself,
我知道你在说自己，
why should I keep my hand going on just a half note,
为什么我要把手放在二分音符上，
I'm going to get worn out,
我会筋疲力尽的，
I'm going to die early, die young in my life,
我会在我的生命中早逝，
because I'm wasting all my energy doing this,
因为我在浪费我所有的能量，
no, you need to keep that,
不，你需要保持这样，
because as we get more and more complex with our rhythms,
因为随着我们的节奏变得越来越复杂，
if you don't keep that hand going,
如果你不让手移动，
to sound [], you're going to be able to keep up.
声音[]，你能够跟上。
Okay, now, 1b, I'm going to throw that tie in,
好的，现在 1b ，我要把延音线放进来，
we had been going down, down up, down,
我们一直是下，下上，下，
now, I'm just going to take away one of those downs,
现在，我要把其中一次下拿掉，
and see what happens,
看看会发生什么，
down, down up,
下，下上，
down, down up, down up, down up,
下，下上，下上，下上，
you're ending your strum on up beat,
你的扫弦在上拍上结束，
feels kind of funny.
感觉有点好笑。
Okay, let's try one more time,
好的，让我们再试一次，
down, down up,
下，下上，
a little bit faster,
再快一点，
there you go,
就是这样，
take a while for you to kind of get the concept of this,
花点时间让你理解一下，
down up, down up.
下上，下上。
Let's do number two,
我们来做第二个，
the first part is a, without the tie,
它的第一部分是 a ，没有延音线，
down, down up, down up, down,
下，下上，下上，下，
again,
再来一次，
when I have the tie in,
当我加上延音线的时候，
it then becomes down, down up, up, down,
它就变成了下，下上，上，下，
down, down up, up, down,
下，下上，上，下，
okay, again, don't get confused,
好的，再说一次，不要糊涂了，
what's the rule, keep your hand going,
规则是什么，保持你的手移动，
if your hand is always going,
如果你的手一直在移动，
you'll end up being in the right part of the cycle to land on it,
你最终会落在它的正确位置上，
one more time, 2b,
再来一次， 2b ，
down, down up, up, down,
下，下上，上，下，
I'll slow it down even a little more,
我会让它更慢一点，
down, down up,
下，下上，
there's a silent down there,
这里有一个无声的下，
then we come back into it.
然后我们回到它。
Great, let's do number three, without the tie first,
好的，我们来做第三个，首先是没有延音线的，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
keep your hand going,
保持你的手移动，
again.
再来一次。
Okay, now the b section,
好的，现在 b 部分，
I'm gonna throw that tie in,
我要把延音线加进来，
down up, keep your hand going,
下上，保持你的手移动，
down up, down up, keep your hands going,
下上，下上，保持你的手移动，
a little bit faster,
更快一点，
a little bit faster, go,
更快一点，开始，
one more go,
再来一次，开始，
very good, here you go, great, okay.
非常好，继续，很好。
Now, I think we're ready for suspended chords,
现在，我认为我们已经准备好挂留和弦，
okay, we're just going to cover three of them,
好的，我们将介绍其中的三个，
this will be the last of our basic chords,
这将是我们的最后一个基本和弦，
you have covered probably close to twenty chords in the last,
你最终需要掌握大概 20 个和弦，
this session and past sessions,
这节课和前几节课，
so we have crammed a lot of chords into you, in a very short amount of time,
我们在很短的时间里塞进了很多和弦，
may take a while to process all of those,
可能需要一段时间才能处理完，
the last three we're going to cover are suspended chords,
我们将讨论的最后三个和弦都是挂留和弦，
suspended chords is just a way of referring to,
挂留和弦只是一种方式，
they're going to take the third note of the scale and suspend it up to the fourth.
它们会取第三个音符，然后把它[暂停]到第四个音符。
We'll learn a little bit more about the mechanics of that a little bit,
我们将学习更多关于这一点的机制，
but just realize it's related to the major chord.
但要意识到它与大调和弦有关。
A, our major chord is like this,
A我们的主要和弦是这样的。
now for suspended chords,
现在，对于挂留和弦，
suspended chords almost always involve your pinky,
挂留和弦几乎总是涉及到你的小指，
slide that pinky out just one fret,
滑动小指一个品格，
that's an Asus.
这是 Asus 。
Now, you may be saying yourself,
现在你可能会对自己说，
well why don't I just play it like this,
为什么我不像这样演奏呢，
well, that's a possibility,
这是有可能的，
but let's talk about why that's not a good idea,
但让我们谈谈为什么这不是一个好主意，
suspended chords almost always come right next to a major chord,
挂留和弦几乎总是紧挨着一个大和弦，
it's kind of like a [] and a you,
就像是[]和你，
you always seen together,
你总是看起来在一起，
like if I'm playing A,
如果我演奏 A ，
see I'm just putting my pinky out,
看到我只是伸出我的小拇指，
if I did it the other way, it wouldn't work,
如果我使用另一种方式，它不会起作用，
I have to really whack out my hand in order to get to work,
我必须真的伸出我的手才能开始工作，
so it's much easier to do with your pinky,
所以，使用你的小拇指更容易做，
that's why I encourage you to learn that way.
这就是为什么我鼓励你学习这种方式。
Okay, Dsus as the next one,
好的， Dsus 是下一个，
okay, now look carefully at the numbers on that chord block,
好的，现在仔细看和弦上的数字，
tells you where those where to put your fingers,
告诉你手指放在哪里，
it may seem odd at first,
一开始可能看起来很奇怪，
but remember we're relating it to the major chord,
但记住我们把它和大和弦联系在一起，
here's a D,
这是 D ，
I just put my pinky down,
我只是把我的小拇指放下来，
that's a Dsus,
这是 Dsus ，
don't play like that, that's not a good way to play it,
不要像这样弹奏，这不是一个好的方式，
play it with a D, Dsus,
伴随 D 弹奏， Dsus ，
D, Dsus,
D Dsus ，
on all the suspended chords,
在所有的挂留和弦上，
I'm just moving my pinky,
我只是在移动我的小拇指，
see how that works.
看到它是如何工作的。
Now, the next one, the last one is an E, and Esus,
下一个，最后一个是 E ， Esus ，
we start with the E,
我们从 E 开始，
Esus, sneak that pinky right underneath there,
Esus ，把小指挂在下面，
it's kind of like an A chord,
它有点像 A 和弦，
just you moved everything up the string set,
只是把所有的东西都往上移了，
okay back to E.
好的，回到 E ，
Now, if you want to take your first finger off,
现在，如果你想把你的食指拿开，
it really doesn't matter,
这无关紧要，
because it's being covered by the pinky anyway,
因为它被小指遮住了，
I don't know, I might just go and leave it on.
我不知道我可能会把它留在上面，
Okay, alright now move on to your suspended chord exercises,
好的，现在转到你们的挂留和弦练习，
let's go through a couple of those,
让我们练习一下，
starting with number one, starts on an A,
从练习一开始，从 A 开始，
look at the rhythm,
看着节奏，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
Asus, slide pinky out,
Asus ，把小拇指滑下来，
keep that hand going,
保持手移动，
Asus go,
Asus 继续，
that's a little quick,
这有点快，
let's try, that let's slow that down just a little bit,
让我们试着慢一点，
same thing,
同样的东西，
play,
弹奏，
keep your hand going
保持你的手移动，
Asus,
Asus ，
D go,
D 继续，
there you go, much better.
干得不错，好多了。
Okay, now, number two we're going to start throwing those ties in,
好的，练习二，我们将加入延音线，
okay, look at that rhythm,
好的，看看节奏，
starts on a D,
从 D 开始，
quarter to eight going into that half note with a tie,
四分音符到八分音符，到加延音线的二分音符，
keep your hand going, that's the rule,
保持你的手移动，这是规则，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
listen to it first,
先听一下，
down up, keep your hand going,
下上，保持你的手移动，
Dsus,
Dsus ，
now to a G,
现在切换到 G ，
Dsus.
Dsus 。
Good, it all works out,
一切都解决了，
if you remember to keep that hand going,
如果你记得保持手的移动，
try it one more time,
再试一次，
now a G go, Dsus,
现在是 G ， Dsus ，
here you go.
干得好。
Very good, let's do, let's see number three,
很好，让我们来做练习三，
give us a little workout on that Esus.
给我们一点 Esus 的练习。
Okay, look at this rhythm,
好的，看这个节奏，
down, down up, down, down, down up, down,
下，下上，下，下，下上，下，
here we go, number three,
我们开始，练习三，
we will start slow,
我们开始会慢一点，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
down, down up, down, Esus,
下，下上，下， Esus ，
a little bit faster,
稍微快一点，
my hand always going down up, down up, down up, down up, down up, down,
我的手总是在下上，下上，下上，下上，下上，下，
my hand is always going in that cycle,
我的手总是在这个循环中，
as soon as you start getting a tempo
一旦你开始有节奏，
and even when we're just counting things off,
即使当我们只是在数东西的时候，
get that hand started down up, down up,
让你的手开始，下上，下上，
and things will work out better.
事情就会变得更好。
Okay, welcome to the guitar tips section,
好的，欢迎来到吉他技巧部分，
in this section, we're going to give you three main strumming patterns,
在这一部分，我们将给你三种主要的扫弦模式，
now I don't want to get so lost in the downs and downs up,
现在我不想迷失在下，下上，
am I am down on my up,
我是不是在上的时候弹了下，
don't get too worried about that,
不要太担心，
let me play the rhythm,
让我来弹奏节奏，
you play it back,
你再来弹，
and then we'll kind of do it together
然后我们会一起做，
and I want you want you kind of got the flow of it,
我希望你能顺其自然，
not to look at the page anymore
不再看页面，
and just to listen and see if you can get the flow of it,
只是倾听，看看你能不能顺其自然，
once you kind of get the flow of it,
一旦你顺其自然，
it starts working a whole lot better.
它就开始工作得更好了。
We're just gonna go on a G chord,
我们将从 G 和弦开始，
example number one, look at that,
示例一，看看它，
it would be down, down up, up, down, down, down up, up, down,
它是下，下上，上，下，下，下上，上，下，
on a G, one two, ready go,
在 G 上， 1 2 ，准备，开始，
just keep doing that for a while,
继续这样做一会儿，
let's switch to a C chord,
让我们切换到 C 和弦，
down, down up, up, down, down, down up, up, down, down, down up,
下，下上，上，下，下，下上，上，下，下，下上，
let's go back to G chord,
让我们回到 G 和弦，
try not to look at the music,
试着不要看乐谱，
try just play it and feel the flow of it,
试着只弹奏它，感受它的流动，
down, down up, up, down,
下，下上，上，下，
C chord,
C 和弦，
let's speed it up a little bit,
让我们快一点，
down up, up, down, down, down up,
下上，上，下，下，下上，
G chord,
G 和弦，
we go a little faster,
我们快一点，
C chord,
C 和弦，
G chord,
G 和弦，
there you go, very good, start like music,
干得好，开始像音乐，
when we speed it up,
当我们加速的时候，
if you break it down,
如果你打破它，
it's just that one pattern,
它只是一个模式，
down, down up, up, down.
下，下上，上，下。
Second one I wanted to cover is a little bit different,
我想要介绍的第二个有点不同，
we just add a little more things to it,
我们只是增加了一些东西，
down up, down up, up, down.
下上，下上，上，下。
Okay, let's try that,
好的，让我们试一下，
same thing on a G chord,
同样在 G 和弦上，
we'll start it slow and then we'll speed up,
我们会慢慢开始，然后再加速，
ready play,
准备，弹奏，
down up, down up, up, down,
下上，下上，上，下，
one more time,
再来一次，
let's go to an Em chord, Em,
让我们切换到 Em 和弦， Em ，
down up, up, down,
下上，上，下，
think about making it smooth,
考虑让它变得顺畅，
there you go, back to G,
干得好，回到 G ，
a little bit faster now,
快一点，
loosen up that wrist,
放松手腕，
a little bit faster, Em.
再快一点， Em 。
Very good, now, the third and last one I want to cover is a little bit different from that,
非常好，我想介绍的第三个也是最后一个略有不同，
look at this one,
看看这个，
down up, up, up, down,
下上，上，上，下，
you got three ups in a row,
你有三个上连在一起，
let's do, let's do it on a C chord,
让我们从 C 和弦开始，
little slow,
慢一点，
ready, play,
准备，弹奏，
down up, up, up, down,
下上，上，上，下，
see when I want to put my fingers on the strings,
当我想把手指放在弦上时，
I just bring that wrist closer,
我只是把手腕拉近，
when I want to take them away, I bring that wrist out,
当我想把弦拿开的时候，我把手腕拿出来，
but that cycle is always going down up, down up, down up,
但这个循环总是下上，下上，下上，
so I can go through all kinds of rhythms,
这样我就可以弹奏各种节奏了，
as long as my hands going keeps in that cycle,
只要我的手在那个循环中不停地移动，
it all works out.
一切都会解决的。
Here's your assignment for this session,
这是你这节课的作业，
I want you to do the minor seventh and the suspended chord exercises in your book,
我希望你做书中的小七和弦和挂留和弦练习，
play through the basic chord songs,
通过基本和弦歌曲，
that we have a schedule for this session as well,
我们对这节课也有一个时间表，
play through them with the notes,
用音符演奏，
so we don't forget our single notes,
这样我们就不会忘记单音符，
since we've been in chord land here for a while
因为我们已经在和弦这里呆了一段时间了，
and I want to also go back and play through with the chords,
我也想回去演奏和弦，
now we've got some strumming patterns to put with these as well,
现在我们已经有了一些扫弦模式，
so it's going to start sounding a whole lot more like music.
所以它会开始听起来更像音乐。
So we'll see at the workshop time.
我们将在 workshop 时间看到。
Okay, welcome to the workshop section,
好的，欢迎来到 workshop 部分，
let's review our minor seventh chords that we learned earlier,
让我们复习我们之前学过的小七和弦，
Am7,
Am7 ，
altogether,
一起，
Dm7,
Dm7 ，
remember our little barre here,
记得我们这里的小横按，
invert that knuckle there,
反转这个指节，
get that sound nice and strong,
让声音听起来好听又有力，
Em7, again there's two ways to do this,
Em7 ，有两种方法可以做到，
or the other way.
或者另一种方法。
Alright, suspended chords, we learned three different types of those,
好的，挂留和弦，我们学习了三种不同类型，
we have Asus,
我们有 Asus ，
remember these use our pinky,
记住用的是我们的小拇指，
Dsus,
Dsus ，
Esus.
Esus 。
Now, we're gonna look at some different chord exercises,
现在我们来看一些不同的和弦练习，
look at the sheet chords in the key of C,
看看 C 调的和弦，
let's do number one,
让我们来做第一个，
remember how we talked about ties with strumming,
记得我们是如何谈论扫弦加延音线的，
this one involves that,
这个涉及到那个，
one of our main strumming patterns,
我们的主要扫弦模式之一，
in fact our first strumming pattern,
我们的第一个扫弦模式，
down, down up, up, down,
下，下上，上，下，
here we go,
我们开始，
chords in the key of C,
用 C 调的和弦，
number one, ready, go,
第一个，准备，开始，
do it again.
再来一次。
Good, number two, ready go,
好的，第二个，准备，开始，
there, works the same way,
同样的方式，
do it again,
再来一次，
down up, down up, up,
下上，下上，上，
G, Em.
G ， Em 。
Number three,
第三个，
one two, number three, go,
1 2 ，第三个，开始，
Dm7, watch that barre.
Dm7 ，注意那个横按。
Let's get down to number five,
让我们到第五个，
two, ready, number five go,
2 ，准备，第五个，开始，
down, down up, up, down up,
下，下上，上，下上，
down down up,
下，下上，
good, do it again, two ready, go.
好的，再来一遍， 2 ，准备，开始。
Six, two three, go,
第六个， 2 3 ，开始，
down up,
下上，
Am7, down, keep that hand going,
Am7 ，下，保持手的移动，
G here,
这里是 G ，
another one, G7,
另一个， G7 ，
a little bit faster, go,
稍微快一点，
Am7, go,
Am7 ，开始，
G, go,
G ，开始，
G7.
G7 。
Okay, now let's look at chords in the key of G,
好的，现在我们来看 G 调的和弦，
okay, look at number one there,
好的，看那里的第一个，
ready go,
准备，开始，
Am.
Am 。
Number two, two, ready, go,
第二个， 2 ，准备，开始，
Em,
Em ，
Am7,
Am7 ，
here comes Dsus,
这里是 Dsus ，
we do that one again,
我们再做一次，
one two, number two again, go,
1 2 ，第二个，开始，
Em,
Em ，
Am7,
Am7 ，
Dsus.
Dsus 。
Good, let's skip down way down number five,
好的，让我们跳到第五个，
check that one out,
看看这个，
starts on a G,
从 G 开始，
ready play,
准备，弹奏，
up, down up, down, down up, up, down up.
上，下上，下，下上，上，下上。
Let's do number six,
让我们来做第六个，
one two, keep that hand going,
1 2 ，保持手的移动，
ready go,
准备，开始，
down up,
下上，
Em7, Am7, D7, G,
Em7 Am7 D7 G ，
one more time, go,
再来一次，开始，
Em7, Am7, D7, G.
Em7 Am7 D7 G 。
Okay, let's look at chord exercises in D, chords in the key of D,
好的，让我们看一下 D 调和弦练习，
okay, let's start off this one,
让我们从这个开始，
let's do number two first,
我们先做第二个，
now I'm kind of skipping around on some of these exercises,
现在我跳过一些练习，
the rest you can kind of do on your own,
剩下的你可以自己做，
but let's look at number two.
但让我们来看看第二个。
Okay, starts on that D7,
好的，从 D7 开始，
one, two and and go,
1 2 ，开始，
Em7, A7 go, G7 here,
Em7 A7 G7 ，
I'm going to repeat, do it again,
我要再重复一遍，
Great, let's do number three,
好的，让我们做第三个，
ready play,
准备，弹奏，
down up, up, down,
下上，上，下，
here comes this Asus,
这里是 Asus ，
back to A,
回到 A ，
a little bit faster, do it again,
稍微快一点，再做一次，
if you find it a bit too fast,
如果你觉得它有点太快了，
just stop it practice a little bit
停下来练习一下，
and see if you can catch up to it when we do it again.
看看我们再做的时候能不能跟上。
Let's skip down to,
让我们跳到，
all of us do number five,
我们所有人做第五个，
ready go,
准备，开始，
down up, down up, up, down,
下上，下上，上，下，
down up, do it again.
下上，再来一次。
Now, I want you to look at number six,
现在，我想让你们看看第六个，
number six is kind of where it gets fun,
第六个很有趣，
it's a little bit more complicated,
它有点复杂，
so it starts sounding like some real music,
所以它开始听起来像一些真正的音乐，
let's take a look at this real slowly.
让我们慢慢地看一下。
Okay, I have you coming in after that D and G, that up,
好的，我让你跟在 D 和 G 之后，那个上，
that's first time we've done this,
这是我们第一次这样做，
so it may take a little practice,
所以可能需要一些练习，
let's do that first measure only,
我们只做第一节，
nice and slow,
慢慢地，
ready go,,
准备，开始，
up down,
上下，
here's that G, up down,
这是 G ，上下，
try it again, just that first measure, go,
再试一次，只是第一节，开始，
down up, down, up, down,
下上，下，上，下，
again, down up, down, up, down,
再来一次，下上，下，上，下，
what's the secret, keep that hand going,
秘密是什么，保持手的移动，
down up, down up, down up, down, there you go.
下上，下上，下上，下，干得好。
Okay, let's play all, going to play all four measures for you,
好的，让我们一起弹奏所有的四个小节，
ready go,
准备，开始，
do do it again,
再做一次，
two, ready, play,
2 ，准备，弹奏，
as speed up,
随着速度加快，
it starts sounding a bit more like a song,
它开始听起来更像歌曲了，
very good, a lot of songs have that same little chord progression.
非常好，很多歌曲都有相同的和弦进程。
Okay, now we're going to talk about,
好的，现在我们要谈谈，
I gave you one song,
我给你的一首歌，
actually there's a couple of songs in there
实际上里面有几首歌，
and remember with all these exercises
记住所有这些练习，
go through every exercise that you can in these books,
你可以在这些书中的每一个练习，
as well, the Jam Along CDs have extra songs on them,
同时 Jam Along CD 上有额外的歌曲，
that you can refer to as well,
你也可以参考，
so you can always have a chance to get as much practice as you need to.
所以你总是有机会得到你需要的尽可能多的练习。
Okay, we're gonna go over one song called greensleeves,
好的，我们将介绍一首名为绿袖子的歌曲，
okay, it's kind of a Christmas song,
好的，这是一首圣诞歌曲，
but a very familiar melody.
但旋律非常熟悉。
Okay, let's take a look at it,
好的，让我们先看一下，
go into the single notes first,
我们首先看单音符，
nice and slow,
慢一点，
it starts on A,
它从 A 开始，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
one two,
1 2 ，
#F,
#F ，
dotted quarter,
加点的四分音符，
#G, #F, #G,
#G #F #G ，
a bit of tricky, finger twister there,
有一点困难，手指在这里扭曲，
A, two three,
A 2 3 ，
another A,
另一个 A ，
next part go,
下一部分，开始，
two three,
2 3 ，
here comes an #F,
这里是 #F ，
G, two three,
G ， 2 3 ，
here it comes again,
又来了，
yeah, really stretch that pinky out to catch that #F.
是的，伸展小拇指去按那个 #F 。
Okay, now I'm gonna play it one more time at tempo,
好的，现在我要再弹一次，
okay, so it'll be a little bit faster this time,
好的，这次会更快一点，
ready, go
准备，开始，
two three.
2 3 。
Great, okay, now we're gonna play the chords with it,
很好，现在我们来弹奏和弦，
I'm going to give you a simple strumming pattern I want you to do,
我会给你一个简单的扫弦模式，
just kind of down, down up, down.
就是下，下上，下。
Okay, three four times,
好的，三四拍，
only three beats are in there,
只有三拍在这里，
down, down up, down.
下，下上，下。
Okay, starts on that Am7,
好的，从 Am7 开始，
ready go,,
准备，开始，
E7,
E7 ，
try make your strums nice and steady.
试着让你的扫弦又好又稳。
Very good, and that Greensleeves,
很好，这是绿袖子，
now leave you to practice on your own
现在让你自己练习，
to speed it up a little bit
让它加快一点，
and make a little more to it,
让它更多一点，
now there's also some other songs in your in your resources that you have available,
现在你的资源中也有一些其他的歌曲，
go ahead and go through as many as you can.
继续，尽可能多地去练习。
Now, before we go in our last minute,
现在，在我们最后一分钟结束之前，
I want to explain to you,
我想向你们解释一下，
you've probably realized by now,
你现在可能已经意识到，
that guitar playing takes a little bit of effort,
弹吉他需要一点努力，
I'm sure you thought that you could just watch a little something and you'd be able to play guitar,
我肯定你认为你只要看一点东西，你就会弹吉他，
but it does take an awful lot of effort,
但这确实需要非常大的努力，
but it's well worth,
但这是非常值得的，
the time and effort that you're putting in into your musicianship, into your,
你投入到音乐事业中的时间和努力是值得的，
making yourself a better person
让你自己变得更好，
by learning how to play guitar,
通过学习如何弹吉他，
yes it's tough and a lot of people quit,
是的，这很困难，很多人放弃了，
but you've stuck around and you're continuing to do it
但你一直在坚持，而且你会继续这样做，
and I think you're going to be the one that reaches the rewards out of this,
我认为你会从中获得回报，
if guitar playing was easy, then everybody would do it,
如果弹吉他很容易，那么每个人都会这么做，
usually everybody can kind of thumb around a few chords,
通常每个人都能摸到几个和弦，
but for folks to actually know what they're doing
但对于真正知道他们在做什么的人们来说，
and get a few more chords and go just beyond average,
多得到几个和弦，并超越平均水平，
it takes some effort
这需要一些努力，
and that's what this is about,
这就是相关的，
in life, there are three kinds of people,
在生活中，有三种人，
there's quitters, campers and climbers,
有放弃者，露营者和登山者，
quitters, look at the task ahead of them,
放弃者，看看他们面前的任务，
they say nah there's no way I could ever do that,
他们说，不，我永远不可能做到这个，
and campers get halfway up
露营者爬到一半，
and they think man, this is as far as I care to go,
他们想，伙计，这是我最想去的地方，
it's just the cost is too much, it takes too much effort,
只是成本太高，需要太多的努力，
but there are those of you that climb
但你们中有一些人需要攀登，
and I want to keep going to try and climb
我想继续攀登，
and to get to the musical levels that they want to get to.
达到他们想要达到的音乐水平。